# JULIA CONNELLY

Software engineer with 5+ years of experience and a B.A. and an M.S. in Computer Science. A quick learning and curious worker experienced with a wide variety of technologies. Enjoys taking ownership of projects. Often recognized for clean code, innovative use of software patterns, and being a fun team member.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **GE Healthcare, Waukesha, WI** — Software Engineer

JULY 2018 - PRESENT

- Worked on the Magnetic Resonance (MR) Image Reconstruction team
- Adapted the reconstruction engine code into a consumable C++, Matlab, and Python SDK for internal and research stakeholders.
- Developed new clinical features in a complex, modern system with multiple communication pathways, micro-services, and custom firmware and hardware.
- Implemented test cases across subsystems at the unit, component, and integration test levels.
- Spent 6 months as a product owner/developer on a team creating a platform solution for safely storing and sharing raw medical imaging data for research purposes.

#### Applied Predictive Technologies, Arlington, VA - Software Intern

JUNE 2017 - AUGUST 2017

- Contributed product code within 1 month of joining the team.
- Collaborated with other engineers, QA, and the product team to implement and test a brand new line chart feature.

### **EDUCATION**

Johns Hopkins M.S. Computer Science

AUGUST 2019 - DECEMBER 2021, Baltimore, MD

Carleton College B.A. Computer Science

September 2014 - JUNE 2018, Northfield, MN

Graduated Cum Laude

# TECHNICAL SKILLS

C# + .NET

Proficient: Competent: C++ Python SOL Server Java + Spring Boot JavaScript HTML/CSS Linux Git OneAPI Docker AWS Lambda AWS EC2 Cucumber Jenkins AWS S3 MATLAB AWS DynamoDB OpenApi

Advanced Beginner:

React Native Firebase Arduino OpenCL Cuda Hadoop Hive Apache Pig Spark

Apache Tomcat